worldcoinindex.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy policy - WorldCoinIndex

WorldCoinIndex (the “Company”) is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Service.

For purposes of this Agreement, “Service” refers to the Company’s service which can be accessed via our website at www.WorldCoinIndex.com. The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to the Company. “You” refers to you, as a user of Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use (found here: Terms and Conditions), you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect “Non-Personal Information” and “Personal Information.” Non-Personal Information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes your name and email, which you submit to us through the registration process at the Site.

_Information collected via Technology:_

In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the Site, to become a subscriber to the Service you will need to create a personal profile. When you create an Account or login using your Facebook, Google credentials or email, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username on that service and/or email address. By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION

_Personal Information:_

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.

_Non-Personal Information:_

In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize the user experience. We also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non- Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to third parties at our discretion. 

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

_About cookies:_

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. 

1 We use cookies for the following purposes:

(a) authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website (cookies used for this purpose are: identify cookies);  
(b) status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website (cookies used for this purpose are: identify cookies);  
(c) personalisation - we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalise the website for you (cookies used for this purpose are: identify cookies);  
(d) cookie consent - we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally (cookies used for this purpose are: identify cookies). 

2 Cookies used by our service providers:

Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.  
(a) We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>.   
You can opt-out of Google Analytics data collection with the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add- on <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>. 

(b) We publish Google Ads interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the web using cookies. 

You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the AdSense partner network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). 

3 Managing cookies:

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via this link: <https://cookies.insites.com/disable-cookies/>. 

## HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION

We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

## YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional e-mail. You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us in the “Settings” section of the Site. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates.

## CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to [support@worldcoinindex.com.](mailto:support@worldcoinindex.com)

**Last Updated** : This Privacy Policy was last updated on 10 February 2019.
